printme.com 2016-05-09

# EFI - Privacy Policy

**Last Updated**

The EFI Privacy Policy was updated on April 28, 2016, and applies to Electronics for Imaging, Inc., and all of its corporate affiliates, including subsidiaries. To view our previous notices, please here.

**In this Privacy Policy, we describe:**

  * Our Commitment to Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Collect Information
  * How We Use Information
  * How We Share Your Information
  * Our Commitment to Data Security
  * Third Party Links
  * Users Outside the United States
  * Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy
  * How You Can Access and Correct Your Information
  * How You Can Opt-Out
  * How to Contact Us
  * Privacy Policy Updates

**  
Our Commitment to Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this Privacy Policy to explain how your information is collected (both online and off-line) and used, and to explain the choices you can make about the way your information is shared. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available by a web link on our homepage.

EFI does not sell or share the Personal Information (defined herein) it collects from you with third parties except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy covers the information practices of EFI and applies to information submitted and collected by, through, or via: (i) an EFI website which includes a reference to this Privacy Policy on the applicable homepage; (ii) any software owned, developed, sold or marketed by EFI; or (iii) any products or services offered by EFI, whether hosted by EFI or a third party (collectively, the “Channels” or individually, the “Channel”), and to information collected off-line by EFI. This Privacy Policy may be subject to any specific and applicable EFI affiliate privacy policy and our privacy practices may vary as required by local law.

Back to top »

**The Information We Collect**

Personal Information: If you wish to contact EFI, we typically ask you to provide personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, contact phone numbers, and email address. This information helps us to reply to you. To use certain Channels, you may be required to complete a registration form and provide contact information (such as name and email address). If you are making a purchase online, we will also require your credit/debit card information, expiration date, billing address, shipping address and related information. We also may ask for your date of birth to register for online forums. You may also provide additional personally identifiable information that you choose to include in an email that you send to us, via a Channel or through a resume you submit in connection with your interest in working for EFI. All of the above personally identifiable information, as well as any other such personally identifiable information that you choose to provide to us, is collectively referred to as “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy. If you refuse to provide the Personal Information that EFI requires in order for EFI to provide you with a product, service or information, you may not receive the product, service or information.

Non-Personal Information: You may provide certain non-personal information to us, such as the products you are using, your company name, your role with your company, electronic information collected through cookies or other similar means, other information in connection with a support request for one of our products, or any other information that you provide or we collect that is not Personal Information. All of this information is collectively referred to as “Non-Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy.

Back to top »

**How We Collect Information**

There are a number of ways in which EFI may collect Personal Information from you. Personal Information may be collected if you provide Personal Information in connection with using a Channel, including ordering a product or service, a webinar registration, Channel forms, faxes, surveys, product registrations, such as registrations associated with the installation of software, use of online tools or programs, responses to mailed materials, subscription to our newsletter and other publications, participation in contests, telephone calls, Channel forums and message boards, and in person, such as at trade shows or other events. In addition, EFI may collect aggregate Non-Personal Information from the Channels that customers access or visit through the use of cookies, clear GIFs and website logs, as described below.

_Cookies:_ EFI may collect Non-Personal Information through the use of cookies. A cookie is a small file that a website puts on a user's hard drive. This file identifies specific information about previous visits to the website. The cookie may store the user's country, language, an assigned random session ID, name and address information or the Internet Protocol (“IP”) address associated with a user’s computer. EFI may use cookies for a variety of purposes, including without limitation: (i) to track the number of users to an EFI website over time; (ii) recognize repeat visits to an EFI website; (iii) to facilitate online navigation and online shopping; (iv) track pages visited during a single online session, analyze trends and gather broad demographic information; (v) adjust the presentation of an EFI website to make it more effective; (vi) store user preferences; (vii) record session information, user-specific information (such as the pages the user accesses or visits) and past activity at an EFI website; (viii) alert users to new Channels that we think might be of value; and (ix) market products and services to users. EFI may link the information it collects by the use of cookies to specific Personal Information. Some of our partners may use cookies on the EFI websites. However, we have no access to or control over those cookies.

Most browser applications allow you to block or limit the use of cookies. Consult the help menu of your browser application for details. If you block the use of cookies, you may not be able to use some of the features on an EFI website.

_Clear GIFs:_ Clear GIFs are small graphic images (in GIF or other image format) placed on a webpage, web-based document, or in an email message. Clear GIFs are invisible to the user because they are typically very small (e.g., only 1-by-1 pixel) and either transparent or the same color as the background of the webpage, document or email message. We do not use clear GIFs to collect Personal Information about you. We may, however, use clear GIFs to capture Non-Personal Information, such as statistical usage information for pages, features or other elements on the Channels or through EFI email messages that are delivered to you. We may correlate this information to a user to personalize user experience and for statistical analysis of user experiences on the Channels or in our emails.

_Website Logs:_ EFI may collect Non-Personal Information in the form of website logs (collectively “Logs”). These Logs are files that record activity on the Channels and gather statistics about users’ activities, such as how many users have visited the Channels, how often, how many “hits” a particular webpage has received, type and quality of the user’s Internet connection to the Channels, and identification of the user’s hardware and software. The entries comprising the Logs may contain IP addresses, user IDs, and identification of the Internet service provider that provides your connection to the Internet. Generally, we use the Logs to operate and improve the Channels, to identify the popularity of certain features, to assist with internal marketing and demographic studies, and to enable us to assess overall efficiency and activity on the Channels.

_Communications Within the Channels:_ EFI may collect information that you submit when posting messages through a Channel forum. Any user communications within the Channels, such as on the forums, should not be considered private and such communications may be viewed and saved by others. EFI is under no obligation to monitor user communications but reserves the right to act on reports of misconduct or abuse of communications privileges. Because communications may be widely viewed and/or heard, we caution users to avoid revealing any Personal Information on the Channel forums.

Back to top »

**How We Use Information**

Information that we collect may be used for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, and we will retain your information for as long as it is necessary. See Privacy Policy Updates for more information on how we provide notice if our privacy practices change.

When you provide us with your Personal Information or Non-Personal Information, we may use such information for a number of purposes including to:

  * Process an order you place for a product or service;
  * Respond to your questions;
  * Provide technical and customer support;
  * Provide you with product news, promotions, and newsletters, including information about events, seminars, updates and helpful tips regarding the products and services of EFI and its partners. Such messages may be provided by email, over the telephone and direct mail. And, if you agree beforehand, via SMS text messaging or social media, such as Facebook or Twitter;
  * Enable online shopping;
  * Enable you to participate in contests;
  * Send you special promotions and commercial advertisements;
  * Contact you with surveys to help us improve the way we do business;
  * Send you information regarding the products and services of EFI and its partners;
  * Allow you to sign up for online services and register products;
  * Create and maintain reseller partnerships;
  * Notify you about administrative matters relating to the Channels and the products and services of EFI and its partners;
  * Improve the products and services of EFI and its partners and the way we do business;
  * Review and, if appropriate, respond to a request to work for EFI; and
  * Improve the functionality and performance of the Channels and services through the use of cookies, clear GIFs and website logs as described above.

Personal Information may be combined with Non-Personal Information. Information collected online may be combined with information collected off-line. Personal Information may be enhanced or merged with data from third parties for the purposes of marketing products or services that may be of interest to you.

Back to top »

EFI may share your information, including Personal Information, within EFI or with any unaffiliated third party, including EFI’s partners, as described in this section. EFI’s partners include independent vendors, suppliers, licensors, contractors, distributors, resellers, dealers, OEMs and other parties who have a business relationship or a potential business relationship with EFI.

Fulfillment of Products and/or Services Provided by or for EFI: EFI may retain other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include, but are not limited to: (i) companies that host or help to administer the Channels; (ii) companies that help to process an order for a product, which may include completing the order, obtaining export clearance, or arranging for shipping and handling; (iii) companies that provide payment and billing services; (iv) companies that conduct surveys or assist EFI in its promotional activities such as contacting you by email or over the telephone; (v) shipping companies that deliver products, third party advertisers or promotional partners who provide a product or service to you; (vi) customer support specialists; (vii) web hosting and internet service providers; and (viii) data analysis firms. Any such third parties who are involved in these activities are authorized to use the information that is collected by and/or disclosed to them for purposes of fulfilling their contractual obligations to EFI, fulfilling any obligations owed to you and to the other individuals who access and use the Channels or services, or as otherwise permitted in this Privacy Policy. EFI requires that any such third parties protect the confidentiality of Personal Information they collect or have access to in the course of their engagement by EFI.

Marketing Materials: From time to time, EFI may share your Personal Information with other companies, so that these third parties may provide you with a special offer or promotion that we think you may find valuable. Unless you specifically tell us that you do not want to receive these special offers, we may share your Information. See How You Can Opt-Out to tell us that you do not want us to share your Personal Information for these purposes.

Sale or Transfer of Information: In the event of a merger, acquisition, spin-off or other transaction related to EFI, an EFI business unit or a portion of EFI’s assets, EFI may transfer the information collected from you, including Personal Information, to the surviving party, acquiring party or other party related to the transaction. You consent to the sale and transfer of your information as described in this paragraph.

Compliance with Law and Fraud Protection: EFI reserves the right to disclose the information it collects from you if EFI believes in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with applicable law or legal process, to avoid liability for EFI and/or its agents and partners, and/or to protect the rights and property (including intellectual property) of EFI and others, including EFI’s agents, partners and customers. Further, EFI may disclose the information it collects if EFI suspects that an individual or entity has provided fraudulent or illegal information, has committed an illegal, fraudulent or wrongful act or omission, has attempted to pose as someone else, or has attempted an unauthorized use or access of any computer system or website.

Back to top »

**Our Commitment to Data Security**

While EFI cannot guarantee complete security of the information we collect from you, we have implemented commercially reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to aid in the prevention of unauthorized access to and improper use of the information we collect from you and to aid in the accurate maintenance of this information. You should be aware, however, that EFI has no control over the security of other websites or services on the Internet that you might visit even when a link may appear to direct you to websites and services from EFI. We want you to feel confident using the Channels; however, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take commercially reasonable steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your Personal Information, other communications or content always will remain secure.

Back to top »

**Third Party Links**

Some EFI websites may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that EFI cannot control and is not responsible for the information collection practices of such websites, which may differ from those of EFI. When you leave an EFI website, we encourage you to read the privacy policies of each website that you visit before providing any information to such websites.

Back to top »

**Users Outside the United States**

The information that EFI collects from you may be collected, transferred to, stored and processed in the United States and any other country in which EFI and its agents and partners maintain facilities. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other applicable countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using a Channel or providing your information to EFI or its agents and partners, you consent to your information being collected, transferred to, stored and processed in the United States and other applicable countries. If you do not agree to this provision, do not provide information to us.

Back to top »

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information through the Channels from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of the Channels are structured to attract anyone under 13. If EFI becomes aware that any person submitting Personal Information to us is under the age of 13, we will delete that Personal Information.

Back to top »

**How You Can Access and Correct Your Information**

You can request access to correct your Personal Information by contacting us at the following:

Email: [privacy@efi.com](mailto:privacy@efi.com)  
Mailing Address:  
Electronics For Imaging, Inc.  
Attention: Privacy Policy  
6750 Dumbarton Circle  
Fremont, CA 94555

You may correct factual errors in your Personal Information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. EFI reserves the right to verify your identity before granting access to this information or making corrections, and reserves the right to deny access to anyone who does not confirm their identity to EFI’s satisfaction.

Back to top »

**How You Can Opt-Out**

You have choices about how your information is used by EFI and shared with third parties. For any commercial emails that you receive from EFI, you have the option to unsubscribe to those messages by following the instructions in the applicable email. Please note that if you unsubscribe, but later request to receive commercial emails from EFI, you will receive these commercial emails and be subject to this Privacy Policy, but will continue to have the right to unsubscribe again if you desire.

You also may contact us as described below to unsubscribe from receiving commercial emails from EFI.

If you do not want EFI to share your Personal Information with third parties so that they may send you information concerning products or services that we believe may be of interest, you may opt-out as described below.

To opt-out, please send an email to [efi@efi.com](mailto:efi@efi.com) as follows:

  * To opt-out of receiving commercial email messages from EFI, include in the subject line of your message: “Remove EFI.”
  * To opt-out of having your information shared with third parties, include in the subject line of your message: “Remove Third Parties.”

Please note that your opt-out rights only apply as described above. EFI may still use and share your information as described in this Privacy Policy to, for example, send you administrative, transactional or relationship messages concerning a product or service you order, otherwise fulfill orders you make or as required by law. See How We Share Your Information for further details. In addition, if your information already has been shared with a third party, like an EFI partner, and you no longer wish to receive commercial emails from that party, you must follow the unsubscribe instructions from the applicable third party.

Back to top »

 **How to Contact Us**

We welcome questions or comments about our Privacy Policy. You may also contact us if you feel that your information is used in a way inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. You can do this by contacting us as follows:

Email: [privacy@efi.com](mailto:privacy@efi.com)  
Mailing Address:  
Electronics For Imaging, Inc.  
Attention: Privacy Policy  
6750 Dumbarton Circle  
Fremont, CA 94555

You may correct factual errors in your Personal Information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. EFI reserves the right to verify your identity before granting access to this information or making corrections, and reserves the right to deny access to anyone who does not confirm their identity to EFI’s satisfaction.

Back to top »

**Privacy Policy Updates**

EFI may revise its Privacy Policy from time to time. Please revisit this site on a regular basis to check for any revisions and EFI’s then-current Privacy Policy. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy.

Date of this Last Policy Update: April 28, 2016

Back to top »
